dreamuniversity.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy | | Dream University

## We Value Your Privacy

We value your privacy and understand that you are concerned about privacy. We consider the information you choose to share with us personal and confidential. Any information you provide us is held with the utmost care, and is not used in ways you have not consented. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information isdescribed below. Please contact us with any questions, comments or suggestions about our privacy policy.

## Security

We are committed to preventing others from unauthorized access to the personal information you provide to us, and we maintain procedures and technology designed for this purpose. We take several steps to protect the information we have about you, including the following:

  * We update and test our technology on a regular basis in order to improve the protection of customer information.
  * We require outside companies and independent contractors to whom we provide customer information for marketing, servicing or processing purposes to restrict the use of the information to those purposes and we prohibit independent use of such information.
  * Access to your information is controlled by strict internal procedures. We maintain policies about the proper physical security of workplaces and records.

## Order Fulfillment

As part of our normal order fulfillment process, we provide the following information to our vendors who in turn provide that information to the shipping provider.

  * Ship to name
  * Ship to address
  * Ship to phone number

## Order Process

During the order fulfillment process, we email you to update you on the status of your order. These emails are typically related order confirmation, shipping notification, delivery notification and shipment delay notifications.

## Newsletters

You can opt-in for our general newsletter and product notifications.

## Direct Mail

When you supply us with your postal address or phone number online you may receive periodic mailings or phone calls from us.

## Unsubscribe Policy

We strive to only send e-mail to those who want to receive it. If you would prefer not to receive future e-mails from us, reply to any email with UNSUBSCRIBE as the subject.

Note: You may not unsubscribe from order status emails. If you do not wish to receive order status emails, please place your order via thetelephone.

## The Information We Collect

If you decide to register on our site, make a purchase request or agree to participate in a promotion, we collect and store the following types of information:

  * Name
  * Address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number
  * Credit Card – We retain only a portion of the credit card number, card type and expiration date. (For example: 1411XXXXXXXX1411)

We need this information to fulfill your order. We may also use this information to customize your experience using our website.

If you order a gift to be sent directly to the recipient, we will ask for the recipient's name, address and telephone number. Any order status emails will be sent to you rather than the recipient. The shipping carrier will need the recipient's phone number in case there are difficulties delivering the order.

## Browser information collected on the web site

We may gather general information about our website and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, goods and services purchased, etc., but in doing so we do not reference you byindividual name, e-mail address, home address, or telephone number. We use this data in the aggregate to determine how much our customers use parts of our site so we can improve the customer experience on our site.We may provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally identifying information without your permission.

As part of our service, we use cookies to store and track information about you on our website. A cookie is a small amount of datathat is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to enhance your experience on our site; remind us who you are and enable us to access your account information so you do not have to re-enter it on subsequent visits; gather statistical information about usage by registered or unregistered users, and research visiting patterns. We prefer you enablecookies on your computer. You will be able to place online orders with us regardless of your whether cookies are enabled on your computer.

## The Way We Use Information

Because our goal is to provide products that best meet your needs, we evaluate your personal interactions with us in an effort to bring youthe products which best suit your tastes. In addition, we use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services.

We may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners, newproducts, services and promotions. At times we may ask you to provide us voluntarily with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests, which we may use to customize our products and services for you.

The email addresses that we collect are used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes and are not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes unless you've requested to receive email offers from carefully selected marketing partners of Dream University®.

If you place a request for products or services, we use your personal information to ship your order; if the products or services arefrom a retail partner, we may provide your relevant information to thatretailer for purposes of the transaction. If you establish a credit account with us or our providers, we collect additional information, including billing information, credit card number and expiration date, and tracking information from checks or money orders.

We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage our website and to enhance our site based on the usage pattern data we receive.

## Children under 13

We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13 without obtaining verifiable consent from their parents. We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our website, and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a child has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), visit the FTC website:[www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

## Marketing Partners

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearingat our site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer. We are not responsible for the data collection and use practices of nonaffiliated marketing partners to which our web site may link.

## Changes to Our Policy

The practices and policies contained in this disclosure are subject to change. Any such changes will be communicated through our website. The practices and policies in this disclosure replace all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject matter.

## Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.

## How to Contact Us

To update, correct or delete your personal information, please contact us. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections or changes.
